<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="<p>Crush concrete on-the-go with a portable concrete crusher. Perfect for construction projects or recycling old materials. Get yours today!</p><p>Learn about the various types of portable concrete crushers available for your construction projects. Choose the best one for your needs today!</p><p>Discover the many benefits of using a portable concrete crusher for your construction projects. Save time, money, and resources with this versatile tool.</p><p>Factors to think about when selecting a portable concrete crusher for your construction needs. Size, capacity, and mobility are key considerations.</p><p>Keep your portable concrete crusher running smoothly with these maintenance tips. Learn how to maximize efficiency and extend the lifespan of your equipment.</p><p>Discover the environmental impact of using portable concrete crushers. Learn how these machines affect our planet and ways to minimize their impact.</p><p>Explore various types of portable concrete crushers for efficient demolition and construction projects. Choose the right one for your needs!</p><p>Portable concrete crusher with powerful jaw crushers for efficient crushing on the go. Perfect for construction sites and demolition projects.</p><p>Powerful impact crushers for portable concrete crushing. Ideal for on-the-go projects and efficient material processing.</p><p>Discover the efficiency of cone crushers in portable concrete crushers. Perfect for crushing hard materials on-the-go.</p><p>Comparison of mobile vs stationary crushers for portable concrete crusher use. Find out which option is best for your construction needs.</p><p>Comparing compact vs fullsize crushers for portable concrete crushing. Find the right size for your project needs.</p><p>Discover the convenience and efficiency of using a portable concrete crusher for your construction projects. Save time and money on-site.</p><p>Boost construction project efficiency with a portable concrete crusher. Save time and labor costs on site. Get more done in less time!</p><p>Save on transport and disposal costs with a portable concrete crusher. Efficiently crush materials on-site and cut down on expenses.</p><p>Recycle onsite materials with a portable concrete crusher for sustainable construction practices. Reduce waste and environmental impact efficiently.</p><p>Portable concrete crusher offers versatility in various job sites, making it the perfect solution for construction projects of all sizes.</p><p>Eco-friendly portable concrete crusher reduces environmental impact compared to traditional methods. Go green with your concrete crushing!</p><p>Important factors to consider when selecting a portable concrete crusher. Make sure to evaluate size, capacity, and mobility for efficient use.</p><p>Ensure compliance with size and weight limitations when using a portable concrete crusher for optimal performance and safety.</p><p>Compare power source options for portable concrete crushers. Choose between electric and diesel for optimal performance and efficiency.</p><p>Portable concrete crusher must have adequate crushing capacity and meet output size requirements for efficient operation on construction sites.</p><p>Portable concrete crusher with mobility features wheels tracks for easy transportation and maneuverability. Perfect for construction projects on the go.</p><p>Stay compliant with regulations and ensure safety with our portable concrete crusher. Prioritize safety features for a worry-free operation.</p><p>Discover essential maintenance tips for portable concrete crushers to ensure optimal performance and longevity. Keep your equipment in top condition!</p><p>Keep your portable concrete crusher running smoothly with regular inspections and cleaning. Ensure optimal performance and longevity for your equipment.</p><p>Ensure smooth operation of your portable concrete crusher with proper lubrication of moving parts. Maximize efficiency and longevity.</p><p>&quot;Keep track of wear parts on your portable concrete crusher for timely replacements. Ensure efficiency and longevity of equipment.&quot;</p><p>Keep your portable concrete crusher in proper storage when not in use to extend its lifespan and ensure it remains in good working condition.</p><p>Train operators on correct usage and maintenance of portable concrete crusher for optimal performance and longevity.</p>">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/grindercrusherscreenlogo1.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Roboto:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
.d2d069e7ffcc81e7931fb055b4f0d5aab{
background-color:#ff0505!important;
border-color:#ff0505!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
.ze48ff60f19b67b6921f6d00d175bc64d:hover{
box-shadow: 0 49.7px 50.3px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
footer{
background:#121212;
color:#ffffff;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.1px 29.7px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.wc2fda786be1c9787042445574057d9e5 p,.wc2fda786be1c9787042445574057d9e5 a,.wc2fda786be1c9787042445574057d9e5 span,.wc2fda786be1c9787042445574057d9e5 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.3px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:7.7px;
padding-right:7.7px;
padding-top:5.4px;
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.x15018d0b9b0fbd939622ed06b1dc726d a{
font-size:16px;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.x15018d0b9b0fbd939622ed06b1dc726d p,.x15018d0b9b0fbd939622ed06b1dc726d span,.x15018d0b9b0fbd939622ed06b1dc726d label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
*{
font-family: 'Roboto', sans-serif;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000;

}
a:hover{
color:#ff0000;background:#000000!important;
}
.wc2fda786be1c9787042445574057d9e5 a,.x15018d0b9b0fbd939622ed06b1dc726d a{
color:#020202!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar-expand-lg navbar">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="index.html"  ><img alt="img/grindercrusherscreenlogo1.jpg" src="img/grindercrusherscreenlogo1.jpg"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="collapse navbar-collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="navbar-nav d-flex ml-auto align-items-center"><li class="nav-item"><a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab nav-link" href="news.html" rel="nofollow" >News</a></li>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab nav-link dropdown-toggle" href="index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Portable Concrete Crusher</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="index.html"  >Portable Concrete Crusher</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="types-of-portable-concrete-crushers.html"  >Types of portable concrete crushers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="benefits-of-using-a-portable-concrete-crusher.html"  >Benefits of using a portable concrete crusher</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="considerations-when-choosing-a-portable-concrete-crusher.html"  >Considerations when choosing a portable concrete crusher</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="maintenance-tips-for-portable-concrete-crushers.html"  >Maintenance tips for portable concrete crushers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="environmental-impact-of-using-portable-concrete-crushers.html"  >Environmental impact of using portable concrete crushers</a>
  
<li class="nav-item  dropdown">
<a class="nav-link w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab dropdown-toggle" href="types-of-portable-concrete-crushers-1.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Types of portable concrete crushers</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="types-of-portable-concrete-crushers-1.html"  >Types of portable concrete crushers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="jaw-crushers.html"  >Jaw crushers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="impact-crushers.html"  >Impact crushers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="cone-crushers.html"  >Cone crushers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="mobile-vs-stationary-crushers.html"  >Mobile vs stationary crushers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="compact-vs-fullsize-crushers.html"  >Compact vs fullsize crushers</a>
  
<li class="nav-item dropdown ">
<a class="nav-link w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab dropdown-toggle" href="benefits-of-using-a-portable-concrete-crusher-1.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Benefits of using a portable concrete crusher</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="benefits-of-using-a-portable-concrete-crusher-1.html"  >Benefits of using a portable concrete crusher</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="increased-efficiency-in-construction-projects.html"  >Increased efficiency in construction projects</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="cost-savings-on-transportation-and-disposal-of-materials.html"  >Cost savings on transportation and disposal of materials</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="ability-to-recycle-onsite-materials.html"  >Ability to recycle onsite materials</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="versatility-in-various-job-sites.html"  >Versatility in various job sites</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="reduced-environmental-impact-compared-to-traditional-methods.html"  >Reduced environmental impact compared to traditional methods</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab dropdown-toggle nav-link" href="considerations-when-choosing-a-portable-concrete-crusher-1.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Considerations when choosing a portable concrete crusher</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="considerations-when-choosing-a-portable-concrete-crusher-1.html"  >Considerations when choosing a portable concrete crusher</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="size-and-weight-limitations.html"  >Size and weight limitations</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="power-source-options-electric-vs-diesel.html"  >Power source options electric vs diesel</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="crushing-capacity-and-output-size-requirements.html"  >Crushing capacity and output size requirements</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="mobility-features-wheels-tracks.html"  >Mobility features wheels tracks</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="safety-features-and-compliance-with-regulations.html"  >Safety features and compliance with regulations</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab dropdown-toggle nav-link" href="maintenance-tips-for-portable-concrete-crushers-1.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Maintenance tips for portable concrete crushers</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="maintenance-tips-for-portable-concrete-crushers-1.html"  >Maintenance tips for portable concrete crushers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="regular-inspections-and-cleaning.html"  >Regular inspections and cleaning</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="lubrication-of-moving-parts.html"  >Lubrication of moving parts</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="monitoring-wear-parts-for-replacement.html"  >Monitoring wear parts for replacement</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="proper-storage-when-not-in-use.html"  >Proper storage when not in use</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="training-operators-on-proper-usage-and-maintenance-techniques.html"  >Training operators on proper usage and maintenance techniques</a>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab nav-link" rel=nofollow href="about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li><li class="nav-item">
<a class="btn-md d2d069e7ffcc81e7931fb055b4f0d5aab btn" href="https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/pages/contact-us" rel="nofollow">Contact Us</a>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for GrinderCrusherScreen</h1>
<p>At GrinderCrusherScreen one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by GrinderCrusherScreen and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in GrinderCrusherScreen. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, GrinderCrusherScreen, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>GrinderCrusherScreen follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of GrinderCrusherScreen.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on GrinderCrusherScreen, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that GrinderCrusherScreen has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>GrinderCrusherScreen's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>GrinderCrusherScreen does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
GrinderCrusherScreen</br>
(770) 433-2670</br>
1772 Corn Rd</br>
Smyrna</br>
GA</br>
https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/</br>
Sales@GrinderCrusherScreen.com</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="pt-5 container py-4" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>GrinderCrusherScreen</p>
<p>Phone : (770) 433-2670</p>
<p>Email : Sales@GrinderCrusherScreen.com</p>
<p>City : Smyrna</p>
<p>State : GA</p>
<p>Zip : 30080</p>
<p>Address : 1772 Corn Rd</p>
<p><a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab" href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/WJM2eCyZzhKaiewk9" rel="nofollow"> Google Business Profile</a></p>
<p>Company Website : <a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab" href="https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/" rel="nofollow">https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="w34b05e24da7f72b9fbad6528aad600ab" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<div>
<p>Follow us</p>
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/GrinderCrusherScreen/" class="facebook w1ecdde5b8c23fcadd6221c96e1ffe9d7" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-facebook"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGLgP54hLfx5XaFQLlJJIpQ" class="youtube w1ecdde5b8c23fcadd6221c96e1ffe9d7" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-youtube"></i></a>
</div>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
